That is, you came grandma who lived in
То есть ты пришёл бабушка которая жила в
Bakhmut Yes Vo You came and said grandma
бахмуте Да Во Ты пришёл и говоришь бабка
you have a bad life under the Nazis,
тебе плохо живётся при нацистах да
[ __ ] your five-story building She went to the well that’s how it
нахрен твою пятиэтажку Пошла в ж вот так
was, you were some soldiers Yes mobiles Zro e
было вы какие-то солдатики Да мобили Зро
Yes, we won’t quarrel or
ие Да мы не будем ссориться или
contract soldiers Well mobiles Zro  or a contract, contract
контрактники Ну мобили Зро или контракт
soldiers, yes, [ __ ], and when the contract
контрактники да да бля а когда контракт
was signed, that's a while ago
подписали вот Давненько
When still in
Когда ещё в
PM It's cool, in short, which brigade do
ПМ Прикольно короче что к какой бригаде
you belong to? We don't have a brigade. We have
относитесь у нас не Бригада У нас
a division. Well,
дивизия Ну дивизия
what division is 119? This is where it is based.
Какая 119 Это где базируется
Perm region Perm Permians like
это Пермский край Пермский Пермяки типа
dadada from the Urals understood Yes, sad Yes
дадада с Урала понял Да печально Да
I just see that Putin is driving the
просто я смотр что Путин гонит зна
Muscovites out, he’s not driving them, in short, to die, but the
москвичей не гонит короче дохнуть а вот
people there are from Buryatia and Perm, in short, damn it,
э людей там с Бурятии с Перми короче
from Tatarstan, damn it, like Scott is driving him to
блин с Татарстана блин как Скотт гонит в
Ukraine to die, sadly, of course, Well,
Украину подыхать печально конечно Ну
you know nothing like that, like the terpilams,
ничего такое это знаешь как терпилам
well, you’ll ride on a yacht, you’ll be there
ну на яхти будет кататься вы будете там
You didn’t choose to lie in the State Budgetary Institution, you didn’t choose
лежать вы не выбирали это вы не выбрали
you. The Motherland called you. Yes, what is life like in general? Where
вас Родина позвала Да такое Как вообще
are you from? The city of
жизнь А вы откуда будете город
Khmelnytsky. How is your life? By the way,
Хмельницкий Как у вас жизнь у Вас кстати
with your division, a lot of people like that
с вашей дивизией уже много типа того
have already died. Yes, I won’t tell you the exact data;
сдохло Да я точные данные не скажу
demographic data, of course, about yours.
демографические конечно по поводу своей
division Yes, but it’s true that there are acquaintances
дивизи Да но знакомые же есть правда
who served with you
которые служили с тобой уже
already. Well, of course there are everywhere. So
того Ну конечно везде есть Так вот
look, this is the most interesting thing. Why they
смотри вот самое интересно Ради чего они
died, I can’t understand. For
сдохли вот не могу понять Ради чего Ясно
what. It’s clear why he’s there for the loot of power. And the
ради чего дет он себе там бабло власть А
boys died,
пацаны сдохли за
why am I in politics?  moments, in principle, I
что я в политические моменты в принципе
don’t bother more like such a humane
не лезу более как такой знаете гуманный
person, you know, who is also aware, in principle,
человек осведомлённый в принципе также и
from
с
TV, so there is an order, there is a
телевизора поэтому есть приказ есть
command, since I am a military man, in
команда так как я военнослужащий я в
principle, I don’t have a second vote, look, I
принципе второго голоса не име смотри
just
вотже
received a large-scale invasion like yes And now
получа го масштабное вторжение типа да И
your colleagues there died in Ukraine
вот твои сослуживцы там дохли в Украине
In short, they were thrown into meat there, damn it, and
Короче их там бросали на мясо блин и
for what? Well, you didn’t
ради чего Ну вот смысл ты не
think about the point. Well, they threw them on meat, very
задумывался Ну что бросали на мясо очень
stupidly, a lot of stupid
глупо очень много глупых командиров
high-ranking commanders who Well, in
высокопоставленных которые Ну в
principle, apparently they only trained to be soldiers.
принципе видимо только на солдатика
And so, if, in principle, everything
обучались А так если бы в принципе всё
would have been done normally in their own  in the rhythm
нормально бы делали бы в своём ритме
mode, I think there would
режиме то я думаю бы и смертей бы
n’t be so many deaths. I saw you. Well, how many
столько не было Я видел ти Ну сколько
guys there in Belogorovka died under
типа там в белогоровке померло под
Avdeevka under Bakhmut?
авдеевкой под бахмутом Там же просто
There’s just a lot of them. In short, you By the way, where were we in what direction were we Artyomovskaya about there a lot of
направлении мы Артёмовская о там много
meat they put yours just c
мяса положили вашего просто ц
just like that  yours turns out that way, look
просто так ваше так получается смотрите
wrong. I’m asking why are you coming, you’re coming
не так Я спрашиваю зачем вот ты прил ты
to a foreign country, like you’ve been given
прил в чужую страну типа тебе дали
an order, you won’t even think about it. I mean,
приказ ты даже не задумаешься А на хера
look at those guys, they died. Yes, sooner
то есть смотри те пацаны умерли Да рано
or later you’ll die too, like that’s how it
или поздно ты тоже помрёшь типа так
turns out. Well, damn, they’ll keep you there
получается Ну блин вас Бут держать там
Until
пока не
you die in a war, we’ll still
сдохните не на войне так всё равно
die at home at work I don’t know from
помрём дома на работе не знаю от
old age yes yes but look like instead of
старости да да но смотри типа вместо
Putin Yes Putin won’t die
того чтобы вот Путин Да Путин не помрёт
in the war Putin won’t die in short at
на войне Путин не помрёт короче на
work but in short he’ll die like
работе да он себе короче помрёт типа
somewhere on a yacht  with chicks,
где-то на яхте с тёлками
yes, that is, it turns out He Yes, he robs your
да то есть получается Он Да грабит ваши
resources Avas sends you to die, in short, I
ресурсы Авас отправляет дохнуть короче
don’t know where and for what
фиг зна куда и ради чего Ладно если бы
Okay, if you understood, I would be interested, well, when I
ты понимал вот Мне было бы интересно ну
meet the military, I understand that he
я когда встречаю военных понимать вот он
says there I want to capture Lvov Personally,
говорит там я хочу захватить Львов Лично
I’m there for example A  Here you guys, it turns out you were
я там например А вот вы Ребята вы
sent, you don’t know
получается вас послали вы не знаете за
what you are for. Tomorrow you will be given an order to leave,
что вы Воте вам завтра дадут приказ уйти
you will leave and you will be happy,
вы уйдёте и будете счастливы
the truth. Personally, I personally, here is my opinion. I am
правда Лично я лично я вот моё мнение Я
not ready now to condemn my
не готов сейчас осуждать своего
ruler, my president, from some
правителя своего президента с какой-то
bad point,
плохой точки
positive early, otherwise  as if he knows
положительной рано иначе как бы он знает
what he is doing And if he is supported by the Armed Forces,
что делает И если его поддерживает ВС а
maybe he is stupid Well, look, maybe he is an
может он тупой Ну как Смотри Может он
old senile man, how does he know what he
старый маразматик как он он знает что
is doing And what is he doing, why can’t he
делает А что он делает почему он не
explain to you what he is doing in 2 years,
может вам объяснить что делает за 2 года
you can explain it, say what it is  h
можно же объяснить сказать то что это ч
Biden This is an old idiot, look,
байден Вот это старый маразматик смотри
comrade Biden didn’t go into Ukraine, didn’t go,
товарищ байден не лез в Украину не лез
in short, damn it didn’t attack Russia, like you
короче блин не нападал типа на Россию Вы
attacked Look, let’s do this, what’s the
напали Смотри вот давай так какая смотри
purpose of your stay in
давай так какая цель твоего пребывания в
Ukraine, the purpose of a special military
Украине цель специально военной
operation to protect civilians in the
операции защита мирного населения на
Donbass What in  [ __ ] you stop stop
Донбассе Какой в жопу ми ты стоп стоп
stop Look you say that you are in the
стоп Смотри ты говоришь что ты на
Artyomovsk direction protecting the civilian
артёмовском направлении защита мирного
population How did you protect the population of
населения Как вы защитили население
Artyomovsk Bakhmut you [ __ ]
артёмовска бахмута вы его нахрен
destroyed it how many people now live in
уничтожили сколько людей сейчас живёт в
Bakhmut we we don’t touch the civilian population again
бахмуте мы мы население гражданское не
look again look
трогаем ещё раз смотри ещё раз смотри
again look before that  how did you come to
ещё раз смотри до того как ты пришёл
protect the population people in Bakhmut
защищать население люди в бахмуте
people in Bakhmut lived and lived peacefully
люди в бахмуте жили да спокойно жили
really Yes friend but you yes stop wait So
правда Да друг но ты да стоп подожди Так
when you came you destroyed Bah stupidly
а вы когда пришли вы уничтожили Бах тупо
destroyed it’s normal that’s adequate again look
уничтожили нормально это адекватно ещё
again Look you look You
раз смотри ещё раз Смотри ты смотри Ты
came again you came  and it was
пришёл ещё раз ты пришёл и уничтожил
not I who destroyed Bakhmut, but we and we did not
бахмут не я а мы и мы не
destroy di in Bakhmut the people who
уничтожали ди в бахмуте люди которые
lived in Bakhmut asked to come and kill our
жили в бахмуте просили приди и убей Наш
city they asked
город просили
you Well, the people who lived in Bakhmut
тебя Ну люди которые жили в бахмуте
asked well the people who lived in
просили хорошо люди которые жили в
Bakhmut asked Putin to come and raze
бахмуте просили Путина приди сравнять с
our city to the ground they asked or
землёй Наш город просили или
no, we are talking about the inhabitants of Bakhmut or something, we are
нет мы сечас про жителей бахмута что ли
talking about the inhabitants of Bakhmut You
говорим про жителей бахмута Вы же
destroyed
уничтожили
Bakhmut, razed it to the ground yes yes
бахмут его сравняли с зем да да В
Basically you contributed it You
основном вы вы приложили е ри Вы Вы
stormed Bakhmut and look again
штурмовали бахмут да ещё раз смотри вы
you are not blood on your hands and there
вы не кровь на твоих руках и в твоих
will be blood in your brains Yes  look, the residents
мозгах будет Да смотри жители ещё раз
ask again, the residents of Bakhmut asked Putin to
спрашиваю жители бахмута просили Путин
free us or you there Emelya, did they
Освободи нас или тебя там Емеля Освободи
ask to free us or
нас просили или
not Okay, I’m a little different now, let’s see
нет Хорошо я чуть-чуть по-другому сейчас
a little bit from the other side,
вот посмотрим чуть-чуть с другой стороны
even a little bit from the other side,
даже обт чуть-чуть с другой стороны
let’s see, answer Look, to watch  on the
посмотрим ответь Смотри чтоб смотреть на
other side answer just look in
другую сторону ответь просто смотри в
Bakhmut in Bakhmut a lot of people lived a lot of
бахмуте в бахмуте жила куча людей куча
people lived quietly they lived
людей жила спокойно
look In Bakhmut people lived calmly
жили смотри В бахмуте жили спокойно люди
the whole population here Milash Tell me Milash
все население вот Милаш Скажи мне Милаш
Aleksandrovich in short yes here you are in your
Александрович короче да вот ты в своих
[ __ ] how long are those 26 years Yes you were still a
бляд сколько те 26 лет Да ты ещ
youngster walking people who  lived in
малолетка шёл людей которые жили в
Bakhmut, pensioners, youth Yes, they all
бахмуте пенсионеры молодёжь Да они все
lived peacefully, studied, played, You came,
спокойно жили учились играли Ты пришёл
freed them from their city, now they
их освободил от ихнего города они теперь
don’t live there, everything was destroyed there in
там не живут всё там уничтожено в
solidarity, people lived, they asked Come,
солидар люди жили они просили Придите
Free
Освободите
us, We, friend, are carrying out the order, so
нас Мы друг выполняем приказ так
I’m saying it right, So what’s your order,
Правильно я говорю Так в чём ваш приказ
look?  your order,
смотри ваш приказ вот
if you look again whenever there were
если смотри ещё раз когда бы когда были
Nazis Yes, Bakhmut lived normally in Bakhmut
нацисты Да в бахмуте бахмут жил
Well, there were some Nazis in Bakhmut
нормально Ну в бахмуте были какие-то
But people lived peacefully, lived in
нацисты Но люди жили спокойно жили в
their houses, didn’t run away from Bakhmut
своих домах никуда не убегали из бахмута
When you came, how many people live in Bakhmut now
Когда вы пришли сколько в бахмуте сейчас
How many
живёт Сколько
people don’t [ __ ] know  doesn’t live because you
человек нихера не живёт потому что вы
came and says People, the Nazis
пришли да и говорит Люди вам нацисты
are stopping you from living, we’re a city nobody lived in. Do you have it this way
мешают жить мы город жил никто У вас так
or
или
not? No again, come on, there are people from
нет Нет ещё раз давай давай есть люди из
Bakhmut who said Come,
бахмута которые говорили Придите нас
Free us, and now they are happy that you
Освободите и сейчас они радуются что вы
freed them, there are
их освободили есть
a lot of them  to the people who are
такие есть очень много народу который
happy that who said
радуется то что которые которые говорили
like yes Come and destroy our Bakhmut
типа да Придите и уничтожьте наш бахмут
and now they are happy that you destroyed where
и сейчас радуется что вы уничтожили где
they live in
они живут в
Bakhmut your military correspondents are showing that Bakhmut
бахмуте ваши военкоры показы что бахмуте
does not live in solidarity Who there nali
не живёт в солидар Кто там нали
understand everything, that is, you came grandma
всё понимаешь то есть ты пришёл бабушка
who lived in Bakhmut Yes  You came and
которая жила в бахмуте Да Во Ты пришёл
said grandma, your life is bad under the
говоришь бабка тебе плохо живётся при
Nazis [ __ ] your five-story building [ __ ] you,
нацистах Да нах твою пятиэтажку Пошла в
that’s how it was, that’s how it
жопу вот так было
turns out Let’s
получается
try again, look at
сво Давай ещ раз попробуем смотри
Yasha, I even find something like that with stupid children, that’s
яши у Я даже к тупым детям типа нахожу
how you find an approach Look,
такой вот как ты нахожу подход Смотри
people lived in bakhmut there  there were some
Жили люди в бахмуте там были какие-то
Nazis Well, people lived normally, the Nazis
нацисты Ну люди нормально жили нацисты
were a lot of Nazis in Bakhmut But
были очень много нацистов в бахмуте Но
people lived peacefully, they went to school, to the
люди жили спокойно ходили в школу в
store, to dances, you came to liberate from the
магазин на танцы пришли вы освободить от
Nazis, you destroyed
нацистов уничтожили
Bakhmut, what are
бахмут
you showing me, my gray
что ты мне показываешь у меня серое
matter is normal Do think, think, think,
вещество нормально Ду думай думай думай
think, let’s go  you have a brown
думай походу у тебя там коричневое
substance there and not a
вещество а не
gray one, my friend. What have you been doing with Donetsk
серое дружок А что вы делали с Донецком
since 1914? Dude, you and your
с четырнадцатого года Чувак ты со своим
breadwinner are generally crooked, like Get lost. At
хлебальник вообще кривым типа Потеряйся
least he looks normal. And you [ __ ] look like a
Он хоть нормально выглядит А ты бля как
loser. Get lost. I’ll talk to him
[__] выглядишь всё Потеряйся я с ним
and everything is like. You just hang out.
поговорю и всё типа А ты себе тусуйся
In short  I'll talk to my dears Milash, in short, is
Короче я с милам поговорю Милаш короче
handsome. He has at least a little bit of
Красава Он хоть немножко у него
brown substance in his head, and you
коричневого вещества голове есть а ты
really [ __ ] look like
бля реально выглядишь как имбицил
some kind of imbecile. In short, look, Milash is like, it turns out
какой-то Короче смотри Милаш типа вот
that you came from Perm, in short,
получается да ты из Перми приехал короче
to free the people in Bakhmut from the Nazis
да чтобы освободить от нацистов людей в
and their Bakhmut is
бахмуте и ихний бахмут
like that  I came to protect Yes, what a peaceful people,
так я приехал защищать Да Мирный народ
look at Bakhmut again
какой так вот смотри в Бах ещё раз
Look, are you really stupid or that there
Смотри ты реально тупой или что в
were peaceful people in Bakhmut, they lived peacefully
бахмуте был Мирный народ он мирно жил
all the damn
всё блин
nits, these ones Yes, they came for money, they
гнида вот эти Да пришли за бабки они
came That’s
пришли Вот и
all, these are all these fairy tales about protecting
всё вот эти все сказки о защите мирного
civilians  and so on Because before
населения и так дальше Потому что до
you came to the people in Bakhmut, they lived in
того как вы припёрлись люди в бахмуте
peace, they didn’t grieve, they went
жили спокойно жили не тужили Да ходили
to discos, they went to schools, they fell in love, they got married, they had
на дискотеки в школы ходили влюблялись
children. Yes, you lived, you
женились детей заводили Да жили вы
came to liberate Bakhmut and destroyed
пришли освободить бахмут и уничтожили
Bakhmut, now no one
бахмут теперь там никто не
lives there, what’s the logic and this is it  very
живёт в чём логика и вот это вот очень
demonstrative Russians Yes, they go there
показательный россияне Да они идут туда
for money Yes, he doesn’t give a damn about people in
за бабки Да ему насрать на людей в
bakhmut Yes, this is an excuse Yes, so that for
бахмуте Да это оправдание Да чтобы себе
some moral reason I went to defend the mines
какой-то морально я пошёл защищать мины
You can’t say that you are a complete scumbag
Ты же не скажешь что ты [__] [__]
who just kills people for money
который просто за деньги убивает людей
Yes, because since -  it’s unpleasant
Да потому что так как-то неприятно
to tell your relatives Yes, first of
сказать родственникам Да себе в первую
all, yes And you’re just a complete scumbag
очередь да А ты просто конченный [__]
who kills people for money and,
который за деньги убивает людей и
under the guise of peaceful people, destroys these
прикрываясь мирными уничтожает этих
peaceful people, destroys their cities, their
мирных уничтожает ихние города ихнюю
lives Burn
жизнь Горите
Doo, subscribe to my Telegram right now,
Ду подпишись на мий Telegram прям зараз
he’s still
он а
very and very
пок це дуже и дуже
polite
важливо
E
E